const facts = [
    {
      "question": "Who has scored the most points in the regular season all time?",
      "answer": "Lebron James"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who has scored the most points in a single game?",
      "answer": "Wilt Chamberlain"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has the most triple doubles in a single season?",
      answer: "Russell Westbrook"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has the most assists in the regular season all time?",
      answer: "John Stockton"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has the most championships?",
      answer: "Bill Russell"
    },
    {
      question: "What state has 4 basketball teams?",
      answer: "California"
    },
    {
      question: "Who holds the all time 3-point record?",
      answer: "Stephen Curry"
    },
    {
      question: "What team drafted Kobe Bryant?",
      answer: "Charlotte Hornets"
    },
    {
      question: "Who has scored the most points in a single All Star game?",
      answer: "Jayson Tatum"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the single team in Canada?",
      answer: "Toronto Raptors"
    }
  ];

export default facts;